go good anna
good job nice backhand turn
very nice
excellent excellent
big turn on the back end shoulder turn
head and match point right here give me
a rip
you're doing so great you're getting a
lot better so what's your training
regimen now
like you play we play once a week no
oh we play once right and then what else
do you do besides that can i play with
some other people
okay great yeah that's great but you
know what everybody's so different
different opponents you get different
like type of shots coming at you
yeah that's great and you do singles
right yeah awesome and you still do the
clinic as well right
um no i haven't done clinics since they
had this uh competition in february i
don't know
what competition i think they had
something
oh like a tournament yes oh you didn't
join
okay you're not quite ready yeah i
didn't go i don't know why
you know all right let's start down down
the road you're going to start competing
too
start playing some matches yeah but you
don't know even know how to do you know
how to keep score
we never did even no i don't i got to
teach you that
okay i got to teach you how to keep
score like 15 love 30 love and all that
and are you practicing your serve you're
not
you have to honor because you can't play
matches without having to surf
the serve is super important you know
what's also great because we have so
many videos now
you can also review the videos do you
ever do that i'm always reviewing the
videos
because like i during the lesson there
is a reactive mode and stuff
yeah but then you sit down and you're
like
yeah watching you can review and you go
into i
and i have a lot of moments because i'm
just watching the video right
you probably like what it is the thing
in a lesson sometimes i tell you so many
things you forget
but you have it on on video you can
always review it
do you ever read the comments um
sometimes sometimes
the comments are i gotta tell you out of
all the comments i get the comments
under your videos are the best
oh yeah yeah i gotta read you something
okay so this guy says the majority of
experienced
players has worse strokes than she had
after this introduction
this was on our first video the beginner
video that we made
so this is really something amazing epic
video no that was an amazing video
because you did so well
right away you picked it up super fast
yeah i fell in love with the game right
away right away right
it's just yeah you like it after dancing
is my
next favorite this is the second passion
yeah very very nice
what's in the bushes here no you're here
she's going crazy
paparazzi what is it
she has a very very nice personality
this guy likes her personality i
i've heard that a lot you know i learned
you know very nice okay let's see here
okay this guy says it would be really
interesting if you could show her
progress in three months
six months etc so this is
actually something that's amazing i
always wanted to have this opportunity
to have someone who i'm teaching like
from scratch but have it
on video because i love teaching
beginners it's one of my favorite things
to do
because i can literally like teach them
from scratch from the beginning
and then you can see the progress of of
how are they improving
but i never had the opportunity to tape
it from day one and then down the road
have it
on video footage so it's definitely
something that uh
we should do like continue to record no
pressure
and then like maybe two years from now
see how good you've gotten
and then have the comparisons you know
from the beginner stage
um to when you get more advanced okay
this guy says beautiful form please
feature her every week
well actually you know as already told
you we decided to take a little bit of a
break
from recording because we don't want it
to ever get repetitive
we want to keep it fresh and exciting
yeah and we don't want to go over the
same lessons like twice we don't have
we want to have repetitive sessions so
we had pretty much all the strokes yeah
and now we're going to take a little bit
of a break like um
maybe two three months and see how
you're progressing then record
again and have like a progress report
you know
it's going to be super hot then yeah
when it was hot like
where was september i think right what
month was it remember i think it was
august maybe august so how many months
have been working already five months
five months this hasn't been that hasn't
been that long
this guy asked is it possible to follow
anna on a social network
is it possible yes of course what is it
follow me everybody
but what is it tell tell people it's a n
a
r o g e r s seven anna rogers seven
that's instagram what about tick tock
are you still doing tech talk i know
i had my but you haven't deleted it no i
have not deleted so what's your tick
tock
i forgot i think it's anna v
one nine seven five and nav197
yeah so everybody go follow follow anna
on the social network
you know you never know good good how
did she repay you for this private
lesson
what is this i read this one
well i'll get into that in a minute we
we do have an agreement i'm sure you
want to
we have an agreement arrangement
we have an arrangement now i'm going to
tell i'm going to tell but i'm going to
respond to it
from uh from a specific question okay
this is interesting this guy says it's
so obvious that she plays golf
the follow through and how she moves the
other leg and her foot after the stroke
you're a golf player no no i've tried it
twice yeah
yeah recently actually okay also like
after we after our beginner session or
yeah yeah that was a couple months ago
i've tried
oh okay so you need it but you haven't
played golf before
no no okay okay anna this is very
interesting um lol
she is not a beginner it is staged
taught
over 10k hours of lessons she's trying
to look like a beginner
oh that's a big compliment seriously but
i'm a stage person that's for sure i
like to
you know were you are you lying to me
all along
no you never played before no that was
our first session
right when we recorded that epic video
yes i've never
i've never played in my life yeah that's
why when i fetch balls you're hitting
everything on with two hands on both
sides
out of all the beginners that i ever
thought i think you progressed the
fastest
that's why i don't blame people who
think this is staged and fake because
it's quite amazing how how much how you
picked it up immediately in that first
session you started hitting balls over
the net
and started cleaning up your technique
because i can tell you that some of the
other beginners
that i teach they have a very difficult
time connecting with the ball they can't
even connect
with the with the strings and the ball
together you know yeah i feel like the
angel is coming out of me when the ball
is coming yeah
it's very natural it's very natural
but um yeah so you you were like you
learned it very very quickly you picked
it up very quickly so
i understand that people think uh it was
staged but it was definitely not
um you were an absolutely 100
complete beginner uh before that first
lesson who's agreed with me that she's
russian
anna what's what will you reveal your
nationality
yes i'm from russia you're from russia
okay all right this guy from siberia
from the coldest part and i
live in here in paradise you know what's
funny you know who else is from siberia
sharapova
yeah this must be this tennis hotspot
a lot of great tennis players from there
all right
totally unfair comment this guy
qualifies it right away but anna seems
to be more interested in the opportunity
to have
a bunch of new skimpy outfits than
anything else
okay no the thing is like i honestly
didn't have time to invest into clothes
for tennis yeah
exactly i just think it's not my number
one priority
whatever skimpy i have home i wear right
you don't have you didn't especially
that first lesson you didn't have any uh
tennis clothes this is a little lemon
but i don't think it's for
uh there's nothing that's ridiculous
don't even listen
to it don't listen to that don't listen
to that people don't realize
it's very warm here i mean like i don't
know how else to dress but lightly
you gotta dress lightly exactly it's 90
degrees out anna this guy says
i can almost see her brain grow new
connections second by second she is so
smart
oh i agree i didn't notice my brain
yes very sometimes it comes handy
sometimes really
i'm overthinking the stroke well this is
on your forehand that's what happened
yes see a lot of people are wondering uh
what i'm doing with your forehand
and they were telling me also what to do
on your forehand
oh yeah but i through my experience
i made the decision to go back to your
old forehand
like we talked about because we're going
to develop that loop
a little bit slower than i normally
would with other people because your
interpretation
of the loop was a little bit uh
too mechanical so you were obsessing on
the loop it was too much in your head
like you said you were thinking about it
too much
and it made the forehand very robotic
and mechanical it didn't look smooth
anymore
yeah and you weren't getting it in they
were missing it a lot when you weren't
playing with me you told me your
forehand was
not working at all in the clinics and
that's why i made the decision to
to slow down on the loop you know to
just build it gradually step by step
and your forehead came back i think it's
been pretty good lately right it's
getting bad
it's getting better ballroom dancer
she's light on her feet definitely helps
a female fetterer
that's a very nice comment oh yeah so
let's just tell the audience you
do ballroom dance yeah i love dancing
right you did competitions and stuff
right i did competitions i perform
um and i love going social dancing
this is like most fun this is cardio
right
yeah and what i find with uh ballroom
dancers
is the weirdest thing i've wasted i'm
teaching actually
two other people that do ballroom dance
and one of them you met remember that
yes
and um everyone that does ballroom dance
is an
unbelievable shape like they don't have
an ounce of fat on them so it
must be in the most amazing workout ever
ballroom dance yes
yeah i'm waiting for you to start oh
right
that's we're going to reveal that later
okay this is an interesting comment
she's
already athletic this coach is amazing
the ability to bring out the best in an
athlete is a great skill she will be on
a women's 3.5 team in no time if she
keeps this up
then when she falls in love with the
game i don't see why she won't be a
solid 4.0 player
so you know what those numbers mean
there's like the rating system
and it's the let's say 5.0 is like the
highest you can get as a recreational
player
and right now i would rate you as a 3-0
you think so i think so okay because
people asked me at the clinic
yeah and they said ask your coach so 3.0
3.0 i think we're going to be 3.5
in a few months okay and then probably
next year we're going to be 4.0 like
improvement in tennis it's very gradual
like you can't just jump
these levels fast you have to be patient
but i think
i think this this um person says 4.0
i actually think you can be 5.0 i think
so but it's going to take a long time
i'm good yeah it's gonna take a lot of
like training you're gonna have to play
as much as possible
muscle memory you're gonna have to start
playing matches you're gonna have to
learn how to keep score
and all that stuff and um i don't see
any reason why you shouldn't
get up to the highest recreational level
this is interesting what a great video i
watched the whole thing with no
intention of playing tennis whatsoever
[Laughter]
it serves different purposes but you
know my goal is to get people to play
tennis
and one thing i do like i get a lot of
beginners to watch me and they start
playing tennis and they
and they write me and say i started
playing playing tennis because of you
i love it but this guy has no intention
of playing and still
had a fun time watching the video so
that's good too i guess
but my but my main goal i do want people
i want to grow the sport you know
i love this game like the one uh i don't
know if you found it
no it's a late uh comment i was just
watching
the video and somebody said the guy
looks like tom brady
i know i saw that i don't see it's a
good one you know
i don't see that at all tom brady yeah i
see that
no yeah no not again maybe like the way
you you squinch your face
i do have a lot yeah yeah yeah you need
the botox you know
i'm gonna pass on that okay i don't
think i'm gonna do that here it is this
guy writes
maybe a next video is of you getting a
lesson in ballroom dancing
uh-huh here we go okay so now so now we
can explain
the entire arrangement between anna and
uh
so i'm teaching you tennis and in return
you were going to teach me ballroom
dancing and while you are
one of the most gifted beginner tennis
players i've ever seen
i am one of the least gifted dancers
probably you've ever seen
so you actually have the the hard
challenge of trying to teach me
that's true it's very true it's very
true no no no i taught him some basic
lessons
basic lessons yes i did you did great
yes of course i'm trying but that's
body weight transfer it's not my
strength awareness but i do see already
like things i don't have time but i do
see some improvements
already in my posture from dancing
that's one of the takeaways every dancer
that i meet they have the most amazing
posture ever
and so do you and maybe that's something
that i can learn from dancing because my
posture has always been
and not the greatest so well you are
like a walking noodle
so speaking of dancing do you want to do
you want to do our lesson that we
normally do do you want to do a
dance lesson real quick yeah all right
all right let's go okay let's do it
okay so which one we're doing today we
are learning bachata
okay all right it's like eight counts
it's very
yeah i think we back up a little bit
very cool music you know anything goes
yeah that's one two three four five
what kind of music is it i'm sorry i
interrupted the teacher but i should
turn on the
i'm going to get copyright strike so
just tell me um
we'll turn on the music um in our heads
we can i'm going to get copyright
strikes oh that's right the music could
be
anything that is going like this if
you're sitting
and you're doing this with your leg okay
in the bar
that means it's bachata it's very like
easy
yes okay one two three four
five six seven eight got it okay three
tap one two three tap tap means you are
not putting body weight on it
so usually okay one all right two three
tap one two three tap
okay wait wait wait and then
and then tap yes let's do it are you
ready i'm ready so which one which way
we're going this way or that way
we are going this way we are facing each
other all right and we are doing this
okay let's go all right ready go